pocodot.com 2011-02-22

# Privacy Policy

At Pocodot, our most important asset is our relationship with you.

Pocodot is committed to maintaining the confidentiality, integrity and security of any personal information about our users. This Privacy & Security Policy explains how we protect personal information provided through our website www.pocodot.com (the "Site") and how we use that information in connection with our service offered through the Site (the "Service"). "Personal information" for purposes of this Policy means information that identifies you, such as your name, address, phone number, fax number or email address.

Pocodot stresses its privacy and security standards to guard against identity theft and provide security for your personal information. We regularly re-evaluate our privacy and security policies and adapt them as necessary to deal with new challenges.

At Pocodot, you can be sure our goal is Privacy. Know that by using Pocodot:

  * 1Your Privacy is not for sale & will NEVER be for sale
  * 2Online session information and use is only used to improve your experience
  * 3Third parties offering other products or services will not be given your personal information without your permission
  * 4You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Login ID and Password 
  * 5Email communication from Pocodot
  * 6Your data is secure
  * 7Changes to your Registration Information
  * 8Contests, Giveaways and Surveys 
  * 9Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law
  * 10Contact us if you have any questions or concerns

Your Privacy is not for sale & will NEVER be for sale(Back to Top)

Simply put, we do not and will not sell or rent your personal information to anyone, for any reason, at any time. Pocodot uses and discloses your personal information only as follows:

to analyze site usage and improve the Service;

to deliver to you any administrative notices, money alerts and communications relevant to your use of the Service;

to fulfill your requests for certain products and services;

for market research, project planning, troubleshooting problems, detecting and protecting against error, fraud or other criminal activity;

to third-party contractors that provide services to Pocodot and are bound by these same privacy restrictions;

to enforce Pocodot's Terms of Use; and

as otherwise set forth in this Privacy and Security Policy.

In the event that you access the Service as brought to you by one of our co-brand partners, through a co-branded URL, your email address used for registration on the Service may be provided to that co-brand partner.

The online session information & uses is used for the sole purpose of improving your user experience while on Pocodot (Back to Top)

This information may be used, for example, to alert you to software compatibility issues, or it may be analyzed to improve our Web design and functionality. "Cookies" are alphanumeric identifiers in the form of text files that are inserted and stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. Pocodot may set and access cookies on your computer to track and store preferential information about you. Pocodot may gather information about you through cookie technology.

Third parties offering other products or services will not be given your personal information without your permission (Back to Top)

Any third party offering other services and/ or products will not be given your personal information without your permission.

You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your Login ID and Password (Back to Top)

If you believe that they have been stolen or been made known to others, you must contact us immediately at [security@pocodot.com](mailto:security@pocodot.com). but in any event you should change your password immediately. We are not responsible if someone else accesses your account through Registration Information they have obtained from you or through a violation by you of this Privacy and Security Policy or the Pocodot.com Terms of Use. If you have a security related concern, please contact us at [security@pocodot.com](mailto:security@pocodot.com). We will work closely with you to ensure a rapid and personal response to your concerns.

Email communications from Pocodot (Back to Top)

We provide our registered customers with weekly summaries of their Account Information and email alerts. You can control / add / change all frequency of communication under the "preferences" tab.

Your data is secure (Back to Top)

At Pocodot we use a combination of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and authentication procedures, among others, to maintain the security of your online session and to protect Pocodot accounts from unauthorized access.

Changes to your Registration Information (Back to Top)

If your Registration Information changes during your subscription to Pocodot, you may update it any time via the Service.

Contests, Giveaways and Surveys (Back to Top)

From time to time, Pocodot may offer you the opportunity to participate in contests, giveaways and other promotions. Any information submitted in connection with such activities will be treated in accordance with this Privacy and Security Policy, except as specifically set forth in the rules for those contests, giveaways or promotions. From time to time, Pocodot may also ask you to participate in surveys designed to help Pocodot improve the Site. Any personal information provided to Pocodot in connection with any survey will be used only in relation to that survey and as elsewhere set forth in this Policy.

Disclosure of your information to protect our rights or if required by law (Back to Top)

Notwithstanding the foregoing, Pocodot reserves the right (and you authorize Pocodot) to share or disclose your personal information when Pocodot determines, in its sole discretion, that the disclosure of such information is necessary or appropriate.

Contact us if you have any questions or concerns (Back to Top)

If you have questions, comments, concerns or feedback regarding this Privacy and Security Policy or any other privacy or security concern, send an e-mail to [security@pocodot.com](mailto:security@pocodot.com).

Pocodot Inc.   
PO Box 8879, Calabasas, CA 91372
